{
    "id": "e0d9686da85640b88027a215dd7d94f6",
    "title": "For, To And So That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She has moved to England ……………………… she can perfect her English.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We send monthly reports ……………………… parents can assess the progress of their children.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He came to Mumbai ……………………… for work.",
            "description": "We use the infinitive to express a person’s purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "to look",
                "for looking"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to Canada ………………………… my brother.",
            "description": "We use the infinitive to express a person’s purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "for seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Send the parcel express ………………………… they will get it before Saturday.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the college ……………………….. an interview with my professor.",
            "description": "We use for to talk about somebody’s purpose in doing something.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A barometer is used ………………………. height above sea level.",
            "description": "We can use for to express the purpose of a thing especially when that thing is the subject of the clause.",
            "answers": [
                "to measure",
                "for measuring",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We use a thermometer ………………………. temperature.",
            "description": "When the clause has a person as subject, we use an infinitive to express the purpose of a thing.",
            "answers": [
                "to measure",
                "for measuring"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a short break ……………………. lunch.",
            "description": "For is a preposition indicating purpose. It goes before a noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Is there anything that I need to get ……………………….. the party?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We left early …………………………… we wouldn’t get stuck in the traffic.",
            "description": "So that is a conjunction used to express purpose. It goes before a clause.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so that",
                "in order that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I worked hard ……………………….. I might pass the test.",
            "description": "The conjunctions so that and in order that are both used to express purpose. ",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}